

# Cyriac Béré

#### Profile

I am a passionate and self-taught developer who enjoy working with web technologies. I have been freelancing since 2015 using JavaScript and building all kinds of software, web and mobile apps and games. I enjoy TypeScript the most and I maintain open source projects on my spare time.

## Employment History

#### Web Development Gig Work at Printech-Tchad

June 2019 - September 2019

- Building websites and admin panels for clients
- Front-End: Gatsby, ReactJS
- Back-end: NodeJS, NestJS, MySQL & TypeORM

## Full-Stack Web Development Gig Work at GLANV, Maroc, Rabat

November 2018 - February 2018

- Building a CRM web app
- Data Visualization
- Front-End: VueJS (SSR NuxtJS)
- Back-end: NodeJS, Typescript, NestJS, MongoDB & TypeORM
- Back-end deployment and maintenance (Devops)

#### Mobile Development Internship at Integrateur-SI, Maroc, Fès

August 2019 - October 2018

- Building an hybrid mobile app with Xamarin
- Integrating a Transport Management System for an ERP
- Editing an existing Angular 4 web app

### Education

Software Engineering Degree, "Université Privée de Fès", Morocco, Fès

October 2018 - July 2020

Software Engineering, "Institut Supérieur d'Ingénierie et des Affaires", Morocco, Fès

October 2017 - July 2018

Computer Science, "Sup'Management", Morocco, Fès

October 2015 - July 2017

#### **Details**

+212 687965194 cyriacbr@gmail.com

#### Links

CV en Français Portfolio LinkedIn Twitter Github 1 Github 2

#### Skills

JavaScript: ES9+, bundlers (Webpack, Rollup), Typescript.

Frontend: VueJS, Angular2+, React, UI/UX Design.

Dev. Mobile: Ionic, React Native, Xamarin, Android.

DevOps & Backend: NodeJS (Express/NestJS), JEE, ASP.Net, Déploiement, CI&CD.

Version Control: Git

#### Languages

French

English